One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Whole Cake Island
جزيرة الكعكة الكاملة
Adventure in the Mysterious Forest
مغامرة في الغابة الغامضة
Ready to launch!
!سننطلق
– I never get tired of looking at it! – Me neither!
أتحمس في كل مرة أراها فيها
Channel 3!
!القناة 3
Here it comes!
ها هي ذي
Shark Submerge III !
!غواصة القِرش 3
I'll take Pedro-san, then.
سآخذ بيدرو-سان إذًا
I'm sorry, Luffy!
أعتذر يا لوفي
I insisted on coming along, but now I'm relying on Brook.
قلتُ إنني سأذهب وحدي، لكنّني أعتمد على بروك
I think I can help you, Pedro-san ! Infiltration is my specialty!
أظن أنه يمكنني مساعدتك يا بيدرو-سان، التسلل هو اختصاصي
I'll get a copy of the poneglyph at any cost!
سأحصل على نسخة من البونغليف مهما كلّف الأمر
Yeah, we'll be counting on you! Brook! Pedro!
أحسنت، سأعتمد عليكما يا بروك وبيدرو
Once we meet up with Sanji and Pudding, we'll be waiting for you around here.
بعدما نلتقي بسانجي وبودينغ، سننتظركما في هذا المكان
We all have to be really careful! Don't forget Pekoms' message!
يجدر بنا جميعًا أن نكون شديدي الحذر، لا تنسوا رسالة بيكومز
"Turn Back"
«عودوا»
Yeah, we decided to go on! We just gotta do it!
لقد قررنا الاستمرار، فلا مجال للتردد
– We're counting on you! – See you!
نعتمد عليكما
Good luck!
حظًا موفقًا
See you later!
أراكما لاحقًا
Okay, let's go!
حسنًا، لنذهب
Depth: 15 meters. Visibility: good.
العمق: 15 مترًا، الرؤية: جيدة
It's going well!
الأمر يسير بشكل جيد
Let's go up the river, straight to Big Mom's castle!
لنذهب على طول النهر نحو قلعة بيغ مام مباشرةً
I hope the river is deep.
آمل أن يكون النهر عميقًا
Thank you for this!
رجاءً
Southwest Coast
الساحل الجنوبي الغربي
Okay, I landed! We've arrived at Big Mom's island!
!هبطنا بسلام، بلغنا جزيرة بيغ مام
– I smell an adventure! – I don't want one!
أشتمّ رائحة المغامرة
As soon as we find Sanji-kun, we'll go back!
سنعود حالما نجد سانجي-كن
We're here, as promised!
نحن هنا كما تواعدنا
Don't shout! The enemy will notice!
لا تصرخ، سيُلاحظنا العدو
Hey, did you really see them, Luffy?
هل أنت متيقن أنك رأيتهما يا لوفي؟
I did! I'm sure!
رأيتهما، بلا شك
But when we looked, they were already gone!
ولكن عندما نظرنا نحن، كانا اختفيا
Yummy! Nami, try and eat the soil! It's hard whipped cream!
ما ألذها! تناولي التربة يا نامي، إنها كريمة مخفوقة صلبة
Yummy!
لذيذة
You're right! It's meringue. Is this island full of candies like the others?
صدقت، إنها مرنغ، أهذه الجزيرة مليئة بالحلوى كالأخريات؟
What?! I wanna live here!
ماذا؟ أُريد أن أعيش هُنا
Around here!
في هذا المكان تقريبًا
I'm sure I saw Sanji and Pudding here, but when I looked away, they were gone!
أنا واثق أنني رأيت سانجي وبودينغ هنا ولكنهما اختفيا عندما أشحت بنظري
This is definitely the southwest coast.
لا شك أن هذا هو الساحل الجنوبي الغربي
And you wouldn't lie about it, but I don't know why they would leave.
وأعلم بأنك لا تكذب، لكنني لا أعلم لِمَ غادرا
I wanna see Sanji already.
أرجو أن نلتقي بسانجي قريبًا
There he is!
ها هو هناك
– Sanji! – What?
سانجي
– What happened? – Hey!
ماذا؟
What's going on?
ما الأمر؟
Sanji was there just now! Why is he hiding?
كان سانجي هناك قبل قليل، لماذا يختبئ؟
Really?
حقًا؟
Sanji?
سانجي؟
What? Where did he go?
ماذا؟ إلى أين ذهب؟
We lost him! But this place looks delicious!
فقدنا أثره، لكن يبدو هذا المكان لذيذًا
It's a forest of sweets!
إنها غابة من الحلوى
It smells so good!
رائحتها حُلوة
If all three of them saw him, it had to be him.
إن رآه ثلاثتهم فلا يمكن أن يكون هذا خطأً
But... why would he disappear?
ولكن لماذا يختفي؟
Sanji-kun...
...سانجي-كن
Believe this, if nothing else.
أرجوك صدقي قولي هذا
I didn't mean to hide anything from my friends.
لم أقصد إخفاء أي شيء عن أصدقائي
Maybe he feels embarrassed.
ربما يشعر بالإحراج
Hey! Sanji! Come on out!
أينك يا سانجي؟ اخرج
We're here to pick you up!
جئننا لنعيدك معنا
Sanji!
سانجي
Okay, let's split up and search!
حسنًا، لنتفرق ونبحث عنه
I'm going this way! Where you see a bunch of cakes!
سأذهب من هُنا، حيث ترون الكثير من الكعك
I'm going straight!
سأذهب للأمام مُباشرةً
Where the sweet caramel-like smell is coming from!
من حيث تأتي الرائحة الشبيهة برائحة الكراميل الحلوة
Then, I'll go this way! Look at those beautiful jellybeans!
سأذهب من هنا إذًا، انظروا إلى حبوب الهلام الظريفة
Wait! I don't want a secondary disaster!
انتظروا، لا أريد مصيبة أخرى
What?! We just lost him, so all we can do is follow our gut.
لماذا تعترضين؟ فقدنا أثره لذا ليس لدينا سوى ملاحقة حدسنا
That's how people who get lost would think.
تفكيرك مشابه لتفكير من ضلّ سبيله
Plus, aren't you guys being motivated by some other cravings?!
إضافةً إلى هذا، ألا تقودكم رغبات قوية أخرى؟
Some other?
أخرى؟
No, we aren't.
لا رغبة لدينا
Don't lie!
كاذب
All right! I'll search with you guys! All three of you, stay with me! Okay?
فهمتكم، سأبحث معكم
Mm-hm. Got it!
حسنًا
– This flower is candy! – Really?!
هذه الزهرة حلوى
This is where the caramel smell comes from!
أتت رائحة الكراميل من هنا
It's so sweet! It sticks to my teeth!
حُلوة جدًا، إنها تلتصق بأسناني
I'm so happy!
أنا سعيدة جدًا
Hey, guys! Do you remember? We're here to pick up Sanji-kun !
هل نسيتم يا رفاق؟ جئنا لأخذ سانجي-كن
You guys are too distracted by the candy!
ألهتكم الحلوى كثيرًا
I thought we were gonna look for Sanji-kun !
ظننتُنا سنبحث عن سانجي-كن
I know!
أعلم هذا
But there are sweets everywhere!
لكن توجد حلويات في كل مكان
Don't you think that's strange?! We're in the enemy's territory!
ألا يثير هذا ريبتكم؟ نحن في منطقة العدو
We'll search to some extent, and if we can't find him, we'll go back.
سنبحث لمدًى معيّن، وإن لم نتمكن من العثور عليه، سنعود
Why?!
...ولكن
This green river! It's melon juice!
هذا النهر الأخضر يجري فيه عصير شمام
Really?! Let me try!
حقًا؟ دعني أتذوقه
If you take a close look at this bridge, it's a donut!
إن أمعنتم النظر بهذا الجسر ستدركوا أنهم عبارة عن دونات
Hey! That's enough!
مهلًا، هذا يكفي
Cross the bridge!
اعبروا الجسر
Nami!
نامي
It's a crocodile!
إنه تمساح
Do you wanna take it down, Luffy?!
هل تريد القضاء عليه يا لوفي؟
No.
كلا
Oh, just humans.
ماذا؟ إنهم بشر
What did you think we were?!
ماذا ظننتَنا؟
That's not important!
هذا ليس مهمًا
The crocodile is wearing clothes and a hat and he talked!
هذا التمساح يرتدي ملابس ويعتمر قبعة وتحدث
Just as I thought, this forest is dangerous and strange!
هذه الغابة خطرة كما توقعت وغريبة
If that surprises you, take a look at us.
هل هذا يفاجئك إلى هذا الحد؟
Well, I know what you mean, but...
...لا، أفهم كلامك
I think we'd better trust Pudding and wait by the sea!
أظنّ أنه من الأفضل لنا الثقة ببودينغ والانتظار عند الساحل
I'm sure she'll bring Sanji-kun !
أنا واثقة أنها ستحضر سانجي-كن
And look! Our road back is already problematic!
وانظروا، قُطع طريق عودتنا
We'll be fine. If we jump over the river, we can always go back.
لا بأس، إن قفزنا فوق النهر سنتمكن من العودة في أي وقت
There's another Luffy?!
يوجد لوفي آخر؟
– Who are you?!
من أنت يا وغد؟
– "Who are you?!" I'm Luffy! Stop mocking me!
من أنا؟ أنا لوفي
What's going on?! Which one is the real Luffy?!
ماذا يحصل؟ أيهما لوفي؟
They move and talk exactly the same!
يتحركان ويتحدثان بنفس الأسلوب
No, they're a bit different!
كلا، إنهما مختلفان قليلًا
Like a mirror image, his scar and accessories and everything are inverted.
كصورة مرآة، ندبته وملحقاته وكل شيء معكوس
It really looks like there's a mirror! Who is that?!
يبدو مثل المرآة بالفعل، من الآخر؟
Who are you?!
من تكون؟
– She's asking who you are! Answer her, you idiot!
تسأل من أنت أجِبها، أيها الغبي
There he is! I found Sanji!
ها هو ذا وجدت سانجي
There! Up in the tree!
هناك في الشجرة بالأعلى
Hey! Sanji!
يا سانجي
Get out of my way, you fool!
ابتعد عن طريقي، أيها الغبي
Sanji-kun, what are you doing up there?!
سانجي-كن، ماذا تفعل بالأعلى هناك؟
Oh, he's running again! Sanji!
إنه يهرب ثانيةً سانجي
You bastard! Outta my way!
أيها الوَغد ابتعد عن طريقي
Damn! You guys, go ahead! Chase him!
سحقًا أيها الرفاق، اذهبوا الحقوا به
O-Okay!
حـ-حسنًا
I'm coming too!
سأذهب معك
Don't get separated! Chopper! Carrot!
لا تنفصلا عنا يا تشوبر وكاروت
This forest is strange! Something's gonna happen again!
هذه الغابة غريبة، سيحصل شيء ما ثانيةً
I know! But if we lose Sanji again...
...أعلم هذا، لكن إن فقدنا سانجي ثانيةً
Sanji!
سانجي
Nami, go with them!
نامي، اذهبي معهما
I'll catch up with you after I beat him up!
سأتبعكم بعد أن أضربه
Yeah, okay!
نعم، فهمت
Sanji!
سانجي
Gum-Gum...
غومو غومو نو
Gatling!
غاتلينغ
Who the hell are you?!
من تكون يا هذا؟
Th-There's a humongous half-buried man!
يو-يوجد شخص هائل الحجم شبه مدفون
It's a giant!
إنه عملاق
– You scared me! – We should be saying that!
أخفتموني
Are you okay?! Who did this to you?!
هل أنتَ بخير؟ من فعل بك هذا؟
Your body is half buried!
جسدك شبه مدفون
I'm half buried because I want to be.
أحب أن أكون شبه مدفون
The thing is...
...الأمر هو
I wanna have some juice.
أنني أريد شرب بعض العصير
I don't care!
لا أهتم
Chopper, don't take him seriously! He'll drive you crazy!
لا تأخذه على محمل الجد يا تشوبر، سيصيبك الجنون
Wait, wait, you guys.
انتظروا، انتظروا، يا هؤلاء
He's saying something.
إنه يقول شيئًا
Ignore him!
تجاهليه
I like apple juice very much.
أحب عصير التفاح كثيرًا
– So what?! – Don't listen to him.
وما همنا؟
If you go left, there are waterfalls of apple juice.
إن اتجهتم لليسار، ستعثرون على شلّال من عصير التفاح
I like them very much.
أحبه كثيرًا
Remember what Luffy told us? We should be looking for Sanji-kun.
هل تذكر ما أخبرنا به لوفي؟ يجب أن نبحث عن سانجي-كن
Am I dreaming?
هل أحلم؟
You're looking for someone, aren't you? He came this way.
أنتم تبحثون عن شخص، لقد مرّ من هنا
I said, "Don't take him seriously!"
ألم أقل لك ألا تأخذه على محمل الجد؟
If you get me some apple juice, I'll tell you.
سأخبركم إن أتيتموني بشيء من عصير التفاح
Okay, okay.
حسنًا، حسنًا
Watch out! Nami! Chopper!
احذرا يا نامي وتشوبر
A rabbit?!
أرنب؟
No! Let's run!
إياكِ، لنهرب
There are talking trees and crocodiles, and the rabbit was trying to kill us!
ثمة أشجار وتماسيح متكلمة وكان الأرنب يحاول قتلنا
This place is weird. Let's go back to see Luffy!
هذا المكان غريب، لنَعُد إلى لوفي
We still know the way!
لا يزال بوسعنا العودة من نفس الطريق
But, what about Sanji?!
لكن ماذا بشأن سانجي؟
We don't know if he was real or not anymore!
لا علم لنا إن كان الحقيقي أم لا؟
We finally saw each other, but he didn't even get up!
،لم نلتق منذ مدة ولكنه لم يستقبلنا بحفاوة
He didn't say anything!
ولم ينبس ببنت شفة
And if that's the real Sanji-kun,
وإن كان ذلك سانجي-كن الحقيقي
do you think he'd just stand by and watch us going through this?!
هل تظنه سيبقى دون حراك يشاهدنا نمرُّ بهذه المتاعب؟
All right. Let's go back.
حسنًا، لنعُد
The needles are...
...الإبَر قد
Look! The clock is like that, too!
انظروا، الساعات أيضًا
Everything about this forest is strange!
كلّ شيءٍ بشأن هذه الغابة غريب
♪ Did you hear that? ♪
♪ هل سمعتَ هذا؟ ♪
♪ Yes, I did! ♪
♪ نعم، سمعت ♪
♪ Move over! ♪
♪ تحرّكوا♪
♪ Tree, tree, tree, tree! ♪
♪ شجرَة، شجرَة، شجرَة، شجرَة♪
Whole Cake Island's Southwest Coast
الساحل الجنوبي الغربي لجزيرة الكعكة الكاملة غابة \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hالإغواء
♪ Close up their way out! ♪
♪ اغلِقوا طريق خُروجهم♪
♪ Flower! Flower! Flower! ♪
♪ زهرة زهرة زهرة ♪
♪ Let's play! ♪
♪ لنَلعب♪
♪ Let's play a murder game! ♪
♪ لنَلعب لُعبة قتل ♪
– Chopper, can't you go faster?! – This is the fastest I can go!
اسرع أكثر يا تشوبر
Is he coming?
هل هو قادم؟
Yeah, he's coming after us!
نعم، إنه يتبعنا
We gotta get out of this forest as soon as possible!
يجب أن نخرج من هذه الغابة بأقصى سرعة
Yeah!
نعم
That rabbit is formidable!
ذلك الأرنب قوي
But he's not a mink!
لكنه ليس من المينك
Are you sure?!
هل أنتِ واثقة؟
Did he eat a devil fruit?
هل هو آكل فاكهة شيطان؟
♪ They've noticed! ♪
♪ لَقد لاحظوا ♪
♪ The Straw Hats have noticed! ♪
♪ لَقد لاحظ قراصنة قُبّعة القشّ ♪
♪ Us! ♪
♪ أمرنا ♪
♪ – No, they haven't – There's something wrong! ♪
♪ كلّا، لَم يفعلوا - هناك خطبٌ ما - ♪
♪ They've noticed! ♪
♪ لَقد لاحظوا ♪
♪ – Madame Brûlée is... – ...playing with them! ♪
♪ ...بروليه-ساما - تلعب معهم... -♪
♪ Whose prey are they? ♪
♪ من سيجعلهم فريسته؟ ♪
♪ It would be delicious if we were to make smoothies out of them! ♪
♪ سيكون من اللّذيذ إن صنعنا شراب سموذي منهم♪
See! He can't use Electro!
أتريان؟ لا يُمكنه استخدام الكهرباء
Take this!
خُذ هذه
– Carrot! Stay with us! – Okay!
ابقي معنا يا كاروت
I'm sorry, Bird-san !
حسنًا
"Crane Rider" Randolph Big Mom Pirates
راندولف، راكب طائر الكركي - قراصنة بيغ مام
– The weapon is... – ...coming toward us!
...السلاح
Big Mom's castle, Whole Cake Chateau.
قلعة بيغ مام، قصر الكعكة الكاملة
The lake behind it is called Lake Aprico.
البحيرة التي تقع خلفها تدعى بحيرة أبريكو
This is Germa's ship! Requesting permission to enter the port!
هذه سفينة جيرما، نطلب الإذن لدخول المرفأ
Go ahead!
تقدموا
Only the ships of Big Mom's subordinates
القراصنة التابعون لبيغ مام
or those soon to join her empire, are allowed entry.
وأولئك الذين سيصبحون تابعين قريبًا يُسمح لهم بدخول المرفأ
Keep it coming! Keep it coming!
استمروا بالتقدم، استمروا بالتقدم
All right. Stop right there!
حسنًا، توقفوا هناك
Brace for the impact!
استعدوا للاصطدام
Germa is
...جيرما هو
the name of the one and only seafaring kingdom that has no land of its own.
اسم المملكة الوحيدة المرتحلة عبر البحار والتي لا تملك أرضًا تخصها...
Several dozen of their ships travel independently,
العديد من سفنها تسافر مستقلة بالعادة
but occasionally come together to form the shape of the kingdom.
ولكن أحيانًا تجتمع هذه السفن لتشكل مملكة عائمة
The country is ruled by the Vinsmoke family,
هذه الدولة سيطرت على الأزرق الشمالي بالقوة فيما مضى تحت حكم عائلة فينسموك
This is the Kingdom of Germa.
هذه مملكة جيرما
Their army, Germa 66, is still viewed as a threat in the world.
وإلى يومنا هذا، يعتبر العالم جيرما 66 تهديد قائم
Most of its citizens are men and soldiers.
معظم مواطنيها رجال وجنود
There is not a day that they don't train themselves.
ولا يمرُّ يوم دون أن يتدربوا
Why don't you go away already?
إلى متى ستبقين جالسة مكانك؟
How could you say that...
...ما أقسى كلامك
to your sister who you haven't seen for 13 years?
لأختك التي لم ترَها منذ 13 عامًا؟...
How many times do I have to tell you?
ألا تفقهون قولي؟
I cut ties with you guys under no uncertain terms!
قطعتُ علاقاتي بكم دون أي لبس
You guys must be crazy to put up a tasteless picture like this!
أنتم مجانين تعلقون صورة لئيمة كهذه
The big incident where four kings in the North Blue were put down.
الحادثة الضخمة التي قُتِل فيها ملوك الأزرق الشمالي الأربعة
The Conquest of Four Nations.
غزو الأمم الأربعة
Our father's dream is to bring the North Blue under Germa's control again.
حلم أبينا هو إخضاع الأزرق الشمالي تحت سيطرة جيرما ثانيةً
What's wrong with that?
ما المشكلة في هذا؟
It's natural for men to seek power and fame.
من الطبيعي أن يتعلق الرجال بالقوة والشهرة
Why don't you enjoy being a member of privileged royalty
...تخلي عن طاقم القراصنة العفنّ ذلك
rather than staying in a silly little pirate group?
وتمتع بامتيازات كونك من العائلة الملكية...
Screw you.
كفاكِ سخفًا
Look. These 10 waiting maids will do whatever you ask them to.
انظر، هؤلاء الخادمات العشر سوف يفعلن ما تأمر به
Don't hesitate to ask, Your Highness.
لا تتردد بالطلب يا سمو الأمير
That's because you're of royal blood.
هذا لأنك من دماء ملكية
If we keep sending our troops to countries in war, we'll never run out of money.
إن واصلنا إرسال جنودنا للدول المتحاربة، فلن ينضب المال عنّا
You won't have to fight at all.
لا حاجة لأن تقاتل بنفسك
Don't you like the sound of that?
ألا يعجبك هذا؟
We Vinsmokes have always gained wealth through our force of arms.
نحن عائلة فينسموك اكتسبنا الثروة دائمًا بفضل قواتنا العسكرية
You have that blood in your veins.
تلك الدماء تجري في عروقك
Like I care.
لا يهمني هذا
I'm not gonna marry her!
لن أتزوجها
Pudding is a nice girl, isn't she? I like her.
بودينغ فتاة لطيفة، صحيح؟ فأنا معجبة بها
Generalissimo, where are you going?
أيها القائد العام، إلى أين تذهب؟
I'm gonna go see Sanji.
سأذهب لرؤية سانجي
Don't bother me.
لا تزعجني
Esteemed Father, why are you here?
أبي، لماذا أنت هنا؟
Vinsmoke Judge King of Germa and Generalissimo of Germa 66
فينسموك جادج، ملك مملكة جيرما القائد العام لجيرما 66
Are you still whining?
أما زلت تتذمر؟
You bastard...
أيها الوغد
Oh, my son.
ولدي
Don't call me that.
لا تدعُني بهذا
Even if I call someone "Father", it wouldn't be you!
حتى لو اعترفت بك والدًا لي، فلن أناديكَ أبي مطلقًا
Did you do something to Yonji? He is quite strong.
ماذا فعلت بيونجي؟ فهو قوي جدًا
I guess I'm stronger than him!
أنا أقوى منه فحسب
Step outside!
!اخرج
Men should talk with their fists.
الرجال يتحدثون بقبضاتهم
The Seducing Woods
غابة الإغواء
Chopper! Carrot! Dodge!
تفادياه يا تشوبر وكاروت
Okay!
حسنًا
What's going on back there...?
ماذا يحصل في الخلف هناك؟
He can serve as a landmark!
سنستدل على طريقنا بوجود هذا الشخص
The field of lollipops!
حقل الحلوى العودية
A little more to go until we reach Luffy!
نكاد نصل إلى مكان لوفي
You bastard! Outta my way!
أيها الوغد
– He's still fighting! – Luffy!
ما زال يقاتل
Let's go back to the coast!
لنعد إلى الساحل
Oh? Why're you guys here?!
لماذا رجعتم إلى هنا؟
Hurry up! I'll tell you later!
أسرع، سأخبرك لاحقًا
This forest has a bunch of creepy traps!
هذه الغابة مليئة بالفخاخ المخيفة
Okay!
حسنًا
Somebody's after us!
أحدهم يلاحقنا
Let's get out of the forest as fast as we can!
لنخرج من الغابة بأقصى سرعة
That's the river where we saw the talking crocodile!
انظروا، إنه النهر الذي رأينا فيه التمساح المتكلم
If I remember right, as soon as we cross the river, we can get out!
حسبما أذكر، سنقترب من المخرج إذا تجاوزنا نهر الشمام
Let's jump over it like this!
لنقفز فوقه إذًا
Here we go!
ها نحن ذا
Wait, guys! That's not the real m–
-انتظروا يا رفاق الذي معكم ليس أنـ
Did you say something, Luffy?!
أقلت شيئًا يا لوفي؟
No, I didn't.
كلا، لم أقل
Guys! Let's keep running without slowing down!
استمروا بالركض يا رفاق، ولا تبطئوا
Okay!
حسنًا
What happened to Sanji?!
ماذا حلّ بسانجي؟
He ran away from us and didn't come back!
هرب منا ولم يعد
Something's wrong with him, even though he sure looks like Sanji!
ثمة خطب به، ولكنه يشبه سانجي-كن بالتأكيد
Let's talk after we get out, Nami!
لنتحدث بعد أن نخرج يا نامي
Yeah! I'm glad that we still know the way!
نعم، من حسن الحظ أننا عرفنا الطريق
We'll reach the coast soon!
سنصل إلى الساحل قريبًا
– Huh? – What?
!عجبًا
Oh, it's you guys again!
أرجعتم ثانيةً يا هؤلاء؟
Hey, could you pull out the thing that's stuck to my...
اسحبوا ذلك الشيء الذي علق بقي آنفًا
We just went straight back the way we came!
عدنا من حيث أتينا تارةً أخرى
Why are you here?!
لماذا أنت هنا؟
Don't yell. It scares me.
لا ترفعي صوتك، فهذا يخيفني
Did you ask why I'm here? I was here the whole time!
أتسألين لماذا أنا هنا؟ وأنا لم أتحرك من هنا طوال الوقت؟
It's you guys that left and came back.
أنتم من غادرتم وعدتم
– Chopper, let's try again! – Uh-huh!
لنتجه إلى المخرج ثانيةً يا تشوبر
Hey! Pull out the thing that's stuck in my head!
انتظروا، اسحبوا الشيء العالق في رأسي
Running through the field of lollipops...
...نركض عبر حقل الحلوى العودية
Jumping over the crocodile's river...
...نقفز فوق نهر التمساح
Let's get to the coast this time!
لنصل إلى الساحل هذه المرة
You scared me!
أخفتموني
Why do you guys keep coming back here?
لماذا تستمرون بالعودة؟
Again?! Even without the log pose working,
،ثانيةً؟ حتّى دون عمل البوصلة المسجلة
we don't need to know the directions, because it's one simple path!
لا نحتاج لمعرفة الاتجاهات لأنه طريق واحد بسيط
Going straight back this way...
...لنعود مباشرة من هنا
Slowly... Slowly...
...ببطء... ببطء
Oops.
سحقًا
The soil is moving and talking!
التربة تتحرك وتتكلم
What's going on?
ماذا يحصل؟
What are those things? What's with this forest?!
ما تلك الأشياء؟ ما أمر هذه الغابة؟
– They found out! – They did!
اكتشفوا الأمر - اكتشفوا -
♪ Flower! ♪
♪ زهرة زهرة♪
There was no path from the beginning!
لم يكن هناك طريق من الأساس
You finally became aware...
أدركتم أخيرًا
of the terror of this forest!
رعب هذه الغابة
Hey, Luffy, what are you doing?!
مهلًا يا لوفي، ماذا تفعل؟
This is the Seducing Woods!
هذه غابة الإغواء
Nami! That's not Luffy!
ذلك ليس لوفي يا نامي
Who are you?!
من أنتِ؟
Who am I?
من أنا؟
We were together the whole time!
كنا معًا طوال الوقت
No matter how many times you try, you'll never get out of this forest!
مهما حاولتم الهرب، لن تخرجوا من هذه الغابة أبدًا
Never...
أبدًا
Not until you die!
حتى توافيكم المنية
Let go of me!
اتركيني
Calm down, young girl.
اهدئي أيتها الشابة
Look at the scar on my face.
انظري إلى الندبة على وجهي
Charlotte Brûlée 8th Daughter of the Charlotte Family
شارلوت بروليه، الابنة الثامنة في عائلة شارلوت
Isn't it terrible?
أليست فظيعة؟
Who are you?! A tree?
من أنت؟ شجرة؟
I'm not a damn tree! I'm Brûlée!
لست شجرة، أنا بروليه
Brûlée?
بروليه؟
A cute rabbit... and a pretty girl...
...أرنبة ظريفة وفتاة جميلة
How nice... When I see your beautiful faces...
...كم هذا لطيف، عندما أرى هذه الوجوه الجميلة
it makes me want to scratch them up!
أرغب بشقها...